Register of the Sino-Judaic Institute records
Hoover Institution Archives
- 2013 Incremental Materials, 1964-2012 (Box 10-32)
  - Exhibit records, 1985-2003
    - Chinese rubbing of 1498, 1997 (Box-folder 32: 1)
    - Dallas exhibit, 2001 (Box-folder 32: 2)
    - Denver exhibit, 2003 (Box-folder 32: 3)
    - Fees, 2001 (Box-folder 32: 4)
    - Film, Beth Hatefutsoth, 2002 (Box-folder 32: 5)
    - Gabow, Leo, notes, 1997 (Box-folder 32: 6)
    - Hilo, Hawaii exhibit, 1998 (Box-folder 32: 7)
    - Inquiry letters, 2000 (Box-folder 32: 8)
    - Jewish Bulletin clipping, 1999 (Box-folder 32: 9)
    - Jewish Community Center, Palo Alto, 1997 (Box-folder 32: 10)
    - Jewish museums, 1999 (Box-folder 32: 11)
    - Jewish Museum of Maryland, 2000 (Box-folder 32: 12)
    - Jewish Museum of New York, 2000 (Box-folder 32: 13)
    - Kaifeng, China, 1997-2002 (Box-folder 32: 14)
    - Koletsky, Sue, 2001 (Box-folder 32: 15)
    - Labels for the 4th wall photos, undated (Box-folder 32: 16)
    - Levine, Pamela, 2001 (Box-folder 32: 17)
    - Narrative, 1990s (Box-folder 32: 18)
    - Negative responses, 2001 (Box-folder 32: 19)
    - Oregon Jewish Museum, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 32: 20)
    - Palo Alto exhibit, 1997 (Box-folder 32: 21)
    - Preparation permission, 1997 (Box-folder 32: 22)
    - Publicity, 1997 (Box-folder 32: 23)
    - San Francisco exhibit, 1985 (Box-folder 32: 24)
    - Slavin, Batsheva, 2000 (Box-folder 32: 25)
    - Supplementary material, undated (Box-folder 32: 26)
    - Toronto, 1997 (Box-folder 32: 27)
    - Traveling agreement, undated (Box-folder 32: 28)
    - Venues, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 32: 29)
    - Zeiden, Cynthia, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 32: 30)
- 2014 Incremental Materials, 1983-2006 (Box 33-35)
  Correspondence and some institutional records, arranged alphabetically.
  - Tiensin history, 1995 (Box-folder 33: 1)
  - Taiwan, 1991 (Box-folder 33: 2)
  - Tang Yating, 1997 (Box-folder 33: 3)
  - Tang Yusheng, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 33: 4)
  - Thomas, Nigel, 1991 (Box-folder 33: 5)
  - Tiananmen Square letter, 1989 (Box-folder 33: 6)
  - Tokayer, Martin, 1991-2001 (Box-folder 33: 7)
  - Topper, Victor H., 1995 (Box-folder 33: 8)
  - Toueg, Rebecca, 1996 (Box-folder 33: 9)
  - Tours, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 33: 10)
  - Transcription of "The Chinese Term for Jews," by Albert E. Dien, undated (Box-folder 33: 11)
  - Trip, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 33: 12)
  - Trusch, Matt, 1998 (Box-folder 33: 13)
  - Tsuriel, Tova, 1993 (Box-folder 33: 14)
  - Cohen, Two-Gun, 1993 (Box-folder 33: 15)
  - U.S. China People's Friendship Association newsletter, 1989 (Box-folder 33: 16)
  - Jewish Heritage Committee of the United Federation of Teachers and the Jewish Labor Committee's Educators Chapter, 1983 (Box-folder 33: 17)
  - United Nations, undated (Box-folder 33: 18)
  - Urumqi, 1991 (Box-folder 33: 19)
  - Soviet Union, Jewish Heritage Society, 1988 (Box-folder 33: 20)
  - Video, 1990 (Box-folder 33: 21)
  - Vienna conference, 1995 (Box-folder 33: 22)
  - Volunteers, 2001 (Box-folder 33: 23)
  - Wahnon, Sheppard, 1992 (Box-folder 33: 24)
  - Wald, Salomon, 2003 (Box-folder 33: 25)
  - Wang Jian, 2003 (Box-folder 33: 26)
  - Wang, Ottilie K., 1990-1995 (Box-folder 33: 27)
  - Wang Ruien, 1995 (Box-folder 33: 28)
  - Wang Xiaoli, 1995 (Box-folder 33: 29)
  - Wang Yisha, 1987-1994 (Box-folder 33: 30)
  - Wang ZhiCheng, undated (Box-folder 33: 31)
  - Warschaw, Carmen, 1991 (Box-folder 33: 32)
  - Wasserman, Martin, 1994 (Box-folder 33: 33)
  - Wasserstein, Bernard, undated (Box-folder 33: 34)
  - Wayside Press, 1997 (Box-folder 33: 35)
  - Weatherhill, Inc., 2001 (Box-folder 33: 36)
  - Website, 1997 (Box-folder 33: 37)
  - Weisz, Tiberiu, 2004 (Box-folder 33: 38)
  - Wei Qianzhi, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 33: 39)
  - Weinbach, Kurt, 1995 (Box-folder 33: 40)
  - Weissman, Nathan J., 1998 (Box-folder 33: 41)
  - Wenzel, Diane, 1998 (Box-folder 34: 1)
  - Simon Wiesenthal Center, 1989-1994 (Box-folder 34: 2)
  - Wong, Sandy, 1994 (Box-folder 34: 3)
  - World Jewish Congress, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 34: 4)
  - Wu Guifu, 1992 (Box-folder 34: 5)
  - Wu Yuan-li, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 34: 6)
  - Wyenn, Than, 1990 (Box-folder 34: 7)
  - Xian, 1986 (Box-folder 34: 8)
  - Xu Boyong, 1994 (Box-folder 34: 9)
  - Xu Buzeng, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 34: 10)
  - Xu Xin, 1990-2006 (Box-folder 34: 11-14)
  - Xu Xin, encyclopedia, 1997-2003 (Box-folder 34: 15)
  - Xu Xin, workshop, 1997 (Box-folder 34: 16)
  - Yan Jun, undated (Box-folder 34: 17)
  - Yao Yi'en, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 35: 1)
  - Yoran, Varda, 1995 (Box-folder 35: 2)
  - Yasue, Hiro, 1997 (Box-folder 35: 3)
  - Yee, Albert, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 35: 4)
  - Yeheskel, Ezra, 1992 (Box-folder 35: 5)
  - Yiddish, 1992 (Box-folder 35: 6)
  - Zhang Moshe Xingwang, undated (Box-folder 35: 7)
  - Zafren, Herbert, 1989 (Box-folder 35: 8)
  - Zhang Qianhong, undated (Box-folder 35: 9)
  - Zhang Sui, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 35: 10)
  - Zhang Tibin, 1991 (Box-folder 35: 11)
  - Zhao, Ed, 1998 (Box-folder 35: 12)
  - Zhao Fusan, undated (Box-folder 35: 13)
  - Zhao Xiangru, 1989-1998 (Box-folder 35: 14-16)
  - Zheng Ying, 1993 (Box-folder 35: 17)
  - Zhou Xun, 1994 (Box-folder 35: 18)
  - Zimman, Jeremy, 1991 (Box-folder 35: 19)
  - Permissions, undated (Box-folder 35: 20)